Guide to the Graphic Communications International Union, Local 767M Records 1908-2009
Special Collections, University of Washington Libraries
- Graphic Communications International Union, Local 767M Records, 1908-2009; 5644-001; 15.38 cubic feet 16 boxes
  - CONTRACTS/CONTRACT NEGOTIATIONS, 1911-2011; SERIES III
    - Contracts/Contract Negotiations, 1911-2011; Subseries A
      - Part 3: Local 767-M Contracts, 1972-2011
        - Duckabuch Book Bindery, 2005 (Box-folder 5/38)
        - Eagle Paper Box, 1982-1999
          - Eagle Paper Box Company Labor Agreements, 1982-2001 (Box-folder 6/18-19)
          - Eagle Paper Box Company Labor Agreements, 1987-1994 (Box-folder 6/20)
          - Eagle Paper Box Company Maintenance Agreement, 1999 (Box-folder 6/22)
        - Epic Press Contract Negotiations, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 7/19)
        - Feline Dezine, 2006-2009 (Box-folder 7/55)
        - Flax, Inc. d/b/a Bergland Typesetting, 1996-1998
          - Flax, Inc. d/b/a Bergland Typesetting Contract Negotiations, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 7/16)
          - Flax, Inc. d/b/a Bergland Typesetting Contract Negotiations, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 7/15)
        - For Color Printing.com Inc. f/k/a Pacific Printing - Contract Negotiations/Grievances, 1999-2003 (Box-folder 4/6)
        - Fraley Enterprises Inc. d/b/a Sun Press, 2000-2006
          - Fraley Enterprises Inc. d/b/a Sun Press Contract Negotiations, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7/49)
          - Fraley Enterprises Inc. d/b/a Sun Press Contract Negotiations, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 7/50)
          - Fraley Enterprises Inc. d/b/a Sun Press Contract Negotiations, 2003-2006 (Box-folder 7/51)
        - Hicks Chatten Company (f/k/a Hicks Chatten Engraving Co.) Contract Negotiations, 1979-2002 (Box-folder 8/31-32)
        - Irwin-Hodson, 1996-2002
          - Irwin-Hodson Contract Negotiations, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 7/33)
          - Irwin-Hodson Contract Negotiations, 1999-2002 (Box-folder 7/32)
        - Keizer Printing & Copying Center Contract Negotiations, 1995-1999 (Box-folder 7/34)
        - Lane Miles Standish Co./Bridgetown Printing, 1994-2006
          - Lane Miles Standish Co. Contract Negotiations, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 5/27)
          - Lane Miles Standish Co. Contract Negotiations, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 5/28)
          - Lane Miles Standish Co. Contract Negotiations, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 5/29)
          - Lane Miles Standish Co. Contract Negotiations, 1999-2000 (Box-folder 5/30)
          - Lane Miles Standish Co. Contract Negotiations, 1999-2003 (Box-folder 5/31)
          - Lane Miles Standish Co. Contract Negotiations, 2003-2006 (Box-folder 5/32)
        - Lithography Northwest Contract Negotiations, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 7/30)
        - L.U.P. Graphics Contract Negotiations, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 7/29)
        - M.C. Graphics Contract Negotiations, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 7/21)
        - Mercury Press Contracts, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 6/2)
        - MICR Print Contract Negotiations/Disclaimer of Interest, 2004-2007 (Box-folder 5/36)
        - Moore Lithograph, Inc., 1975-2005
          - Moore Lithograph, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1994-2000 (Box-folder 4/28)
          - Moore Lithograph, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 4/29)
          - Moore Lithograph, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 2000-2005 (Box-folder 4/30)
        - National Color Graphics, 1991-1997
          - National Color Graphics Contract Negotiations, 1991-1993 (Box-folder 7/25)
          - National Color Graphics Contract Negotiations, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 7/24)
          - National Color Graphics Contract Negotiations, 1997 (Box-folder 7/23)
        - Northgate Litho, 1997-2006
          - Northgate Litho Contract Negotiations, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 12/7)
          - Northgate Litho Contract Negotiations, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 12/6)
          - Northgate Litho Contract Negotiations, 2003-2006 (Box-folder 12/5)
        - Pacific Printing, 1985-1999
          - Pacific Printing Contract Negotiations, 1985-1991 (Box-folder 4/2)
          - Pacific Printing Contract Negotiations, 1988-1993 (Box-folder 4/3)
          - Pacific Printing Contract Negotiations, 1991-1996 (Box-folder 4/4)
          - Pacific Printing Contract Negotiations, 1996-1999; 1986 (Box-folder 4/5)
        - PDX Services, Inc. d/b/a Masterprint, 1994-2008
          - PDX Services, Inc. d/b/a Masterprint Contract Negotiations, 1994-1999 (Box-folder 11/2)
          - PDX Services, Inc. d/b/a Masterprint Contract Negotiations/Disclaimer of Interest, 1999-2008 (Box-folder 11/1)
        - Press Craft, Inc., 1986-2007
          - Press Craft, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 8/23)
          - Press Craft, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 8/22)
          - Press Craft, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 8/21)
          - Press Craft, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 8/20)
          - Press Craft, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1996-1997 (Box-folder 8/19)
          - Press Craft, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 8/18)
          - Press Craft, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 8/17)
          - Press Craft, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1999-2001 (Box-folder 8/16)
          - Press Craft, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 8/15)
          - Press Craft, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 2003-2007 (Box-folder 8/14)
        - The Printing House Contract Negotiations, 1996 (Box-folder 7/18)
        - Print Northwest, 1972-1996
          - Print Northwest Contracts, 1972-1989 (Box-folder 9/1)
          - Print Northwest Contract, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 9/2)
          - Print Northwest Contract, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 9/2)
          - Print Northwest Contract Negotiations, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 9/3)
          - Print Northwest Contract Negotiations, 1989-1996 (Box-folder 9/4)
        - The Print Shop, 2000-2001
          - The Print Shop Contract Negotiations, 2000 (Box-folder 7/47)
          - The Print Shop Contract Negotiations, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 7/48)
        - Quality Trade Service, Inc./Washington Printing Industries Contract Negotiations, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 9/36)
        - Quebecor Integrated Media d/b/a Q-Media Services, 1994-2002
          - Quebecor Purchase of Print Northwest, 1994 (Box-folder 9/7)
          - Quebecor Integrated Media 1996 Contract Negotiations, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 9/10-11)
          - Quebecor Integrated Media - District Council 2 Contract, 1997 (Box-folder 9/7)
          - Q-Media Services (f/k/a Quebecor Integrated Media) 2001 Contract Negotiations, 2000-2002 (Box-folder 9/12)
        - R-4 Printing Contract Negotiations, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 7/27)
        - Rainer Embroidery & Designs, 2001-2010
          - Rainer Embroidery & Designs Contract Negotiations, 2001-2007 (Box-folder 13/9)
          - Rainier Embroidery & Designs Contract Negotiations, 2007-2010 (Box-folder 13/8)
        - Raptor FX f/k/a Eagle ASAP, 1997-2004
          - Eagle ASAP Contract Negotiations, 1997-1998 (Box-folder 8/4)
          - Eagle ASAP Contract Negotiations, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 8/3)
          - Raptor FX F/K/A Eagle ASAP Contract Negotiations, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 8/2)
        - Rono Graphic Communications Co. Contracts, 1990-1998 (Box-folder 8/28)
        - Ross Printing, 1982-
          - Ross Printing Contract Negotiations, 1982-1990 (Box-folder 5/12)
          - Ross Printing Contract Negotiations, 1990-1993 (Box-folder 5/11)
          - Ross Printing - 6/C Press Negotiations, 1991 (Box-folder 5/10)
          - Ross Printing Contract Negotiations, 1990-1996 (Box-folder 5/9)
          - Ross Printing Contract Negotiations, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 5/7)
          - Ross Printing - Press/Prepress Contract, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 5/8)
          - Ross Printing-Bindery Contract Negotiations, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 5/6)
          - Ross Printing-Litho Contract Negotiations, 2000-2003 (Box-folder 5/5)
          - Ross Printing Negotiations, 2003-2004 (Box-folder 5/3-4)
        - Rush Hour Printing Contract Negotiations, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 7/28)
        - Safeco Insurance, 1985-2006
          - Safeco Insurance 1985 Contract Negotiations, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 6/9)
          - Safeco Insurance 1988 Contract Negotiations, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 6/10)
          - Safeco Insurance 1991 Contract Negotiations, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 6/11)
          - Safeco Insurance 1994 Contract Negotiations, 1991-1997 (Box-folder 6/12)
          - Safeco Insurance 1997 Contract Negotiations, 1997-2000 (Box-folder 6/13)
          - Safeco Insurance 2000 Contract Negotiations, 1997-2003 (Box-folder 6/14)
          - Safeco Insurance 2003 Contract Negotiations, 1997-2006 (Box-folder 6/15-16)
          - Safeco Insurance Contract Negotiations, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 6/17)
        - Saturday Night Inc., 2005 (Box-folder 5/37)
        - Sharp Impressions, 1995-2004
          - Sharp Impressions Contract Negotiations, 1996-1999 (Box-folder 5/20)
          - Sharp Impressions Contract Negotiations, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 5/21)
          - Sharp Impressions Contract Negotiations, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 5/22)
        - Shoreline Printing, 1993-2006
          - Shoreline Printing Contract Negotiations, 1993-2003 (Box-folder 5/15)
          - Shoreline Printing Contract Negotiations, 1997-2003 (Box-folder 5/16)
          - Shoreline Printing Contract Negotiations, 2000-2006 (Box-folder 5/17)
        - Skagit Valley Herald, 1985-2001
          - Skagit Valley Herald Contract Negotiations, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 4/42)
          - Skagit Valley Herald Contract Negotiations, 1987-1990 (Box-folder 4/41)
          - Skagit Valley Herald Contract Negotiations, 1990-1992 (Box-folder 4/40)
          - Skagit Valley Herald Contract Negotiations, 1991-1995 (Box-folder 4/39)
          - Skagit Valley Herald Contract Negotiations, 1992-1998 (Box-folder 4/38)
          - Skagit Valley Herald Contract Negotiations, 1992-2001 (Box-folder 4/37)
        - Spokane Custom T-Shirts Contract Negotiations, 1993-1994 (Box-folder 7/26)
        - Stevens-Ness Law Publishing Co. Contract Negotiations, 1995-2001 (Box-folder 7/43)
        - Times Printshop, 1986; 1995-1999
          - Times Printshop Contract Negotiations, 1986; 1995 (Box-folder 7/35)
          - Times Printshop Contract Negotiations, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 7/36)
        - Tom Henderson, 1992-1996
          - Tom Henderson Printing Contract Negotiations, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 5/18)
          - Tom Henderson Printing Contract Negotiations, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 5/19)
        - Tuff T's Screen Printing, 1995-2008
          - Tuff T's Screen Printing Contract Negotiations, 1995-1996; 1986 (Box-folder 11/7)
          - Tuff T's Screen Printing Contract Negotiations, 1996-2000 (Box-folder 11/6)
          - Tuff T's Screen Printing Contract Negotiations, 2000-2004 (Box-folder 11/5)
          - Tuff T's Screen Printing Contract Negotiations, 2004-2008 (Box-folder 11/4)
        - United Graphics Inc. Contracts, 1977-1994 (Box-folder 4/33)
        - US Office Products (formerly Portland Supply House, Inc.), 1996-2001
          - US Office Products (formerly Portland Supply House, Inc.) Contract Negotiations, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 7/37)
          - US Office Products (formerly Portland Supply House, Inc.) Contract Negotiations, 1988-1994 (Box-folder 7/38)
          - US Office Products (formerly Portland Supply House, Inc.) Contract Negotiations, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 7/39)
          - US Office Products (formerly Portland Supply House, Inc.) Contract Negotiations, 1996-1998 (Box-folder 7/40)
          - US Office Products Contract Negotiations, 1998-2001 (Box-folder 7/41)
        - Vyper Sportswear, 1995-2004
          - Vyper Sportswear Contract Negotiations, 1995-1998 (Box-folder 10/1)
          - Vyper Sportswear Contract Negotiations, 1996-2001 (Box-folder 10/2)
          - Vyper Sportswear Contract Negotiations, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 10/3)
      - Part 4: Local 87-B, 1975
        - The Allied Printers Contract, 1975 (Box-folder 13/28)
      - Part 5: Local 202, 1975-1985
        - Moore Lithograph, Inc., 1975-1984
          - Moore Lithograph, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 4/24)
          - Moore Lithograph, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1979-1984 (Box-folder 4/25)
        - Northgate Litho Contract Negotiations, 1975-1985 (Box-folder 12/9)
      - Part 6: Local 530, 1979-1991
        - American-Strevell Contract, 1975-1978 (Box-folder 13/29)
        - Bayless Bindery Contract Negotiations, 1977-1991 (Box-folder 9/35)
        - Columbia Basin Printers & Lithographers, Inc. Contract, 1978-1984 (Box-folder 9/21)
        - Creative Color Services Corporation, 1976-1986 (Box-folder 9/40)
        - Multi-Employer, 1978-1989
          - Multi-Employer Negotiations, 1978-1989 (Box-folder 12/29-31)
          - Multi-Employer Local 530 Contracts, 1979-1983 (Box-folder 8/36)
        - Pacific Printing Contract Negotiations, 1985-1988 (Box-folder 4/1)
        - Press Craft, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1980-1986 (Box-folder 8/24)
        - Safeco Insurance, 1979-1988
          - Safeco Insurance Contract Negotiations, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 6/6)
          - Safeco Insurance Contract Negotiations, 1982-1986 (Box-folder 6/7)
          - Safeco Insurance Contract Negotiations, 1979-1988 (Box-folder 6/8)
        - Seattle Times Local 530, 1983-1985 (Box-folder 12/27)
      - Part 7: Joint Crafts Council, 1981-2006
        - City of Seattle/Joint Crafts Council Contract Negotiations, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 10/14)
        - City of Seattle/Joint Crafts Council Contract Negotiations, 1981-1991 (Box-folder 10/15)
        - City of Seattle/Joint Crafts Council Contract Negotiations, 1986-1989 (Box-folder 10/18-19)
        - City of Seattle/Joint Crafts Council Contract Negotiations, 1991-1994 (Box-folder 10/17)
        - City of Seattle/Joint Crafts Council Contract Negotiations, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 10/20-21)
        - City of Seattle/Joint Crafts Council Contract Negotiations, 1997-2003 (Box-folder 10/22-24)
        - City of Seattle/Joint Crafts Council Contract Negotiations, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 10/25-27)
        - City of Seattle/Joint Crafts Council Contract Negotiations, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 10/28)
        - City of Seattle/Joint Crafts Council Blanket Contract, 2005-2006 (Box-folder 10/29)
      - Part 8: Local 292-M, 1986-1992
        - Butler's Pronto Print Contracts, 1987-1991 (Box-folder 9/27)
        - CF Printing Contract, 1985-1989 (Box-folder 9/28)
        - Dempsey & Campbell Printing Co., 1992-1996
          - Dempsey & Campbell Printing Co. Contract Negotiations, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 4/7)
          - Dempsey & Campbell Printing Co. Contract Negotiations, 1993-1996 (Box-folder 4/8)
        - Hicks-Chatten Engraving Co., 1979-2000
          - Hicks-Chatten Engraving Co. Contract, 1979-1982 (Box-folder 8/29)
          - Hicks-Chatten Engraving Co. Contract, 1992-2000 (Box-folder 8/30)
        - Lane Miles Standish/Bridgetown Printing Contract Negotiations, 1990-1997 (Box-folder 5/39)
        - M.C. Graphics Contract Negotiations, 1994-1996 (Box-folder 7/22)
        - Moore Lithograph, Inc., 1988-1997
          - Moore Lithograph, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 4/26)
          - Moore Lithograph, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1994-1997 (Box-folder 4/27)
        - Multi Employer Local 292-M Contracts, 1986-1992
          - Multi Employer Local 292-M Contracts, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 8/37)
          - Multi Employer Local 292-M Contract Negotiations, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 8/38)
          - Multi Employer Local 292-M Contract Negotiations, 1988-1992 (Box-folder 8/39)
        - Northgate Litho Contract Negotiations, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 12/8)
        - Oregon Catholic Press Contract, 1989-1992 (Box-folder 9/29)
        - Oregon Employing Photoengravers Contracts, 1977-1988 (Box-folder 9/30)
        - PDX Services, Inc. d/b/a Masterprint Contract Negotiations, 1995-1997 (Box-folder 11/3)
        - Riddle Press Contract Negotiations, 1992-1995 (Box-folder 9/14)
        - Schultz/Wack/Weir, Inc. Contract Negotiations, 1992 (Box-folder 9/23)
        - Shoreline Printing, 1992-2000
          - Shoreline Printing Contract Negotiations, 1992-1997 (Box-folder 5/14)
          - Shoreline Printing Contract, 1993-2000 (Box-folder 9/25)
        - Smith-Bates Printing Contract Negotiations, 1986-1992 (Box-folder 9/26)
        - Stevens-Ness Law Publishing Co., 1989-1997
          - Stevens-Ness Law Publishing Co. Contract Negotiations, 1989-1994 (Box-folder 7/45-46)
          - Stevens-Ness Law Publishing Co. Contract Negotiations, 1986; 1995-1997 (Box-folder 7/44)
        - Trade Litho Company, 1982-2000
          - Trade Litho Company Contract Negotiations, 1982-1994 (Box-folder 8/35)
          - Trade Litho Company Contract, 1995-2000 (Box-folder 8/34)
        - Twelves Engraving Co. Contract Negotiations, 1988-1991 (Box-folder 9/15)
        - US Office Products (formerly Portland Supply House, Inc.), 1986-1996
          - US Office Products (formerly Portland Supply House, Inc.) Contract Negotiations, 1986-1988 (Box-folder 7/37)
          - US Office Products (formerly Portland Supply House, Inc.) Contract Negotiations, 1988-1994 (Box-folder 7/38)
          - US Office Products (formerly Portland Supply House, Inc.) Contract Negotiations, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 7/39)
        - Zip Instant Press Contract, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 9/16)
      - Part 9: Local 149-B, 1987-1994
        - Eagle Paper Box Company Labor Agreements, 1987-1994 (Box-folder 6/20)
      - Part 10: Blank Printing Contracts, circa 1960s
        - Blank Newspaper Printing Contract, circa 1960s (Box-folder 6/44)
        - Blank Commercial Printing Contract, circa 1960s (Box-folder 6/45)
    - Disclaimers of Interest-Local 767-M, 2001-2007; Subseries B
      - Clinton Hull Printing Disclaimer of Interest, 2004-2007 (Box-folder 5/33)
      - Country Lane, Inc. Disclaimer of Interest, 2004-2006 (Box-folder 5/26)
      - Irwin-Hodson Disclaimer of Interest, 2002 (Box-folder 7/31)
      - M.C. Graphics Disclaimer of Interest, 2001-2002 (Box-folder 7/20)
      - Northgate Litho Disclaimer of Interest, 2006 (Box-folder 12/4)
      - Raptor FX F/K/A Eagle ASAP Disclaimer of Interest, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 8/1)
  - MERGER FILES, 1942; 1963-2004; SERIES IV
    Series IV contains files related to the mergers of local unions, as well as a handful of files related to the mergers of Mail-Well, Inc., a company which was represented by Local 767-M.
    The series is subdivided by originating body: Subseries A: Union Mergers, 1942, 1963-2004; Subseries B: Mail Well, Inc. Mergers, 1993-2002. Within each subseries, files are arranged chronologically.
    - Union Mergers, 1942; 1963-2004; Subseries A
      - Merger of Amalgamated Lithographers of America and International Photo Engravers, 1942; 1963 (Box-folder 13/25)
      - Merger of Locals 202 and 90-B, 1964-1985 (Box-folder 12/20)
      - Merger of Locals 87-B, 203, 23-P forming Local 530, 1974-1985 (Box-folder 12/32)
      - Merger of Locals 49-N and 767-M, 1974-1996 (Box-folder 12/16)
      - Merger of Locals 530-M, 26-N and 50-PH forming Local 767-M, 1976-1991 (Box-folder 12/33-36)
      - Merger of Seattle Locals 87-B, 302 and 23-P, 1976-1991 (Box-folder 12/11)
      - Merger of Locals 367-C and 767-M, 1979-2002 (Box-folder 13/16)
      - Spokane Merger of Locals 81-C and 767-M, 1982-1993 (Box-folder 12/18)
      - Merger Local 767-M and 182-C, 1984-1990 (Box-folder 12/15)
      - Merger of Locals 767-M and 292-M, 1987-1996 (Box-folder 12/12-13)
      - Merger of Locals 767-M and 149-B, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 12/19)
      - Merger of Locals 182-C and 767-M, 2001-2004 (Box-folder 13/17)
    - Mail Well, Inc. Mergers, 1993-2002; Subseries B
      - Mail-Well, Inc. Purchase of American Envelope Company, 1993-1997 (Box-folder 11/20)
      - Rono Graphic Communications Co. Contract/Merger with Mail-Well, Inc., 1995-2000 (Box-folder 8/27)
      - Hicks Chatten Company Contract Negotiations/Merger with Mail-Well, Inc., 1997-2002 (Box-folder 8/33)
      - Mail-Well, Inc. Mergers, 1998 (Box-folder 8/26)
      - Mail-Well Envelope Tukwila Plant Closure, 1999 (Box-folder 11/26)
  - LEGAL FILES, 1911-1953; 1980-2009; SERIES V
    Series V includes arbitrations between Seattle Web Pressmen’s Union no. 26 and the various employers it dealt with. The series also documents the grievance cases between various unions and employers that were brought before the National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) and other official employment commissions. Most cases relate to unfair labor practices or petitions for decertification. While the outcome of these grievances varies greatly, all cases offer insight into the types of problems faced by unions, employees and employers.
    The series is subdivided by function: Subseries A: Arbitrations with Seattle Web Pressmen's Union No. 26, 1911-1953; Subseries B: Grievances, 1980-2001. Subseries B: Grievances, is further divided by case type: Part 1: Unfair Labor Practice Cases, 1980-1981, 1997-2009; Part 2: Petitions for Decertification, 1988-2001; Part 3: Miscellaneous Grievances, 1987-2005. Cases are arranged chronologically within each subseries.
    - Arbitrations with Seattle Web Pressmen's Union No. 26, 1911-1953; Subseries A
      - Arbitration Proceedings Between Seattle Web Pressmen's Union Number 26 and Post-Intelligencer Department Hearst Publishing Company and Seattle Times, 1911-1951 (Box-folder 3/7-8)
      - Arbitrations, 1932-1949 (Box-folder 13/22)
      - Seattle Web Union No. 26 vs. Seattle Times Company and Star Publishing Company Arbitration, 1935 April 8 (Box-folder 3/3)
      - Arbitration between Seattle Post-Intelligencer/Seattle Times Company and Seattle Web Pressmen's Union No. 26, 1952-1953 (Box-folder 13/23)
    - Grievances, 1980-2001; Subseries B
      - Part 1: Unfair Labor Practice Cases, 1980-1981; 1997-2009
        - Moore Lithograph, Inc. - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) Case 36-CB-919, 1980-1981 (Box-folder 4/31)
        - Skagit Valley Herald - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) Cases 19-CA-25905 and 19-CA-26024, 1997-1999 (Box-folder 4/36)
        - Moore Lithograph, Inc. - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) Case 36-CA-8729-1, 2000-2001 (Box-folder 4/32)
        - Dempsey & Campbell Printing Co. - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) Case 36-CA-9430-1, 2003 (Box-folder 4/13-14)
        - MICR Print National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) Case 19-CA-30361, 2006-2009 (Box-folder 5/35)
      - Part 2: Petitions for Decertification, 1988-2005
        - City of Seattle Public Employment Relations Commission Charges, 1988-1990 (Box-folder 10/34)
        - City of Seattle Petition for Union Decertification - Public Employment Relations Council, 1990-1991 (Box-folder 10/33)
        - Skagit Valley Herald - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) Case 19-RD-3351, 1998-1999 (Box-folder 4/35)
        - Ross Printing - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) petition to decertify, 2001-2003 (Box-folder 5/2)
        - Fraley Enterprises Inc. d/b/a Sun Press - National Labor Relations Board (NLRB) Case 19-RD-3718, 2003-2006 (Box-folder 7/53)
        - Reopening of Ross Decertification, 2004-2005 (Box-folder 5/1)
      - Part 3: Miscellaneous Grievances, 1987-2005
        - City of Seattle Mis-classification of Bindery Worker, 1987-1988 (Box-folder 10/35)
        - Schultz/Wack/Weir, Inc. Label Use Grievance, 1992-1993 (Box-folder 9/24)
        - Quebecor Integrated Media - National Labor Relations Board Cases 19-UC-598 and 19-UC-599, 1992-1996 (Box-folder 9/6)
        - Fraley Enterprises Inc. d/b/a Sun Press Wage Grievance - Federal Mediation and Conciliation Service Case #050506-55723-7, 2003-2005 (Box-folder 7/52)
  - OFFICE FILES, 1908-2001; SERIES VI